Guide to the Albert R. Mann papers, 1916-1931.
Mann, Albert R. papers, 1916-1931.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Albert R. Mann papers, 1916-1931.
21-2-14
Albert Russell, Mann 1880-1947.
56.4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, reports, and other papers.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, reports, and other materials relating to the administration of the New York State College of Agriculture at Cornell University, and its departments, units, and enterprises. Papers consist chiefly of correspondence and working papers between the dean and directors and department heads, and pertain to the routine administration and bureaucratic operation of the College; other topics include the Agricultural Experiment Station, relations with the Federal and New York State governments, finance, law and legislation, instruction, faculty benefits, and the Country Life Association. Includes correspondence with Liberty Hyde Bailey.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Albert Russell Mann was born in 1880, and graduated from Cornell University in 1904. After a year in Boston at the Farm School for Destitute Boys, Mann became Dean Liberty Hyde Bailey's personal secretary to assist in the preparation of the Cyclopedia of American Agriculture. In 1908 he was appointed assistant professor of dairy industry, in 1909 secretary to the director, and in 1910 professor of agricultural editing. After a period as Acting Dean, in 1917 Mann became Dean of the New York State College of Agriculture, a position he held until 1931, when he became Provost of Cornell University. He was also the Director of the Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station (1916-1923, 1928-1931), and the Director of Extension (1916-1923). Mann died in 1947.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The Albert R. Mann papers consist of correspondence, reports, and other materials pertaining to the administration of the New York State College of Agriculture and its various departments, units, and enterprises. The papers consist chiefly of correspondence with directors and department heads pertaining to the routine administration and bureaucratic operation of the College; in addition, relations with the New York State and federal governments on questions of finance and law and legislation, and such topics as the Country Life Association and beneficent foundations delineate the papers. Correspondence with Liberty Hyde Bailey is found throughout the papers.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Mann, Albert Russell,1880-1947.; Bailey, L. H.(Liberty Hyde), 1858-1954.; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell University--Faculty.; Country Life Association.; New York State College of Agriculture--Administration.; New York State College of Agriculture.Office of the Dean.
Subjects:
Agriculture--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Cornell University Related Materials
Series II. State and Federal Related Materials
Series III. Subject Matter Files
Series IV. Miscellaneous, A-Z Materials
Arrangement Note
The Mann papers are organized by school year, and are divided into three categories: State and Federal, Cornell University, and Miscellaneous. Researchers should exercise special latitude in searching subjects, as the original filing systems and occasionally unfortunate management systems have resulted in a distortion of the intended topical divisions. Certain folder headings filed in the Cornell file early in Mann's deanship can be found in State and federal later on. Other deviations occur throughout: the categories are not uniformly sequential; some years and groups of records are missing; and headings are subject to variation. There is also a separate topical file at the end of the collection. Original folder headings have been in all cases retained.
CONTAINER LIST
- Cornell University Related Materials, 1917-1931
  - Schurman, President Jacob G., 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Schurman, President Jacob G., 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Schurman, President Jacob G., 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Schurman, President Jacob G., 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Secretary (College), 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    Betten, Cornelius
  - Secretary (College), 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Secretary (College), 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Secretary (University), 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    Patterson, Woodford
  - Sibley College, 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    Kimball, Dexter S.
    White, E. A.
  - Soils, 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    Lyon, T. Lyttleton
    Fippin, Elmer O.
  - Soils, 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Soils, 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Stimson Hall, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Summer School, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - University Christian Association, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Vegetable Gardening, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Work, Paul
    Kirkpatrick, E. L.
  - Vegetable Gardening, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Vegetable Gardening, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Veterinary College, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Moore, V. A.
  - Zoology, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Wright, A. H.
    Reed, H. D.
  - Abstracts, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Wing, H. H.
  - Animal Husbandry, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Architecture, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Attorney (University), 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Attorney (University), 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Botany, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Wiegand, K. M.
  - Botany, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Burritt, Prof. M. C., 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Burritt, Prof. M. C., 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Burritt, Prof. M. C., 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Burritt, Prof. M. C., 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Burritt, Prof. M. C., 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Burritt, Prof. M. C., 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Burritt, Prof. M. C., 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Burritt, Prof. M. C., 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Burritt, Prof. M. C., 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Burritt, Prof. M. C., 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Business Office, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Business Office, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Business Office, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Business Office, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Chemistry, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    Cavanaugh, George W.
  - Civil Engineering, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Commencement Committee, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Committee on Educational Policy, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Committee on Student Affairs, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Comptroller, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Comptroller, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Cornell Countryman, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    Sullivan, E. B.
  - Council, Agricultural College, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Dairy Industry, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    Stocking, W. A.
  - Dairy Industry, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Dairy Industry, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Dairy Industry, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Drawing, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Engineering Department, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    Smith, C. E.
  - Entomology, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    Needham, James G.
  - Entomology, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Entomology, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Entomology, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Extension Committee, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    Van Rensselaer, Martha
  - Extension Teaching, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    Gilkey, R.
    Crosby, D. J.
    Wheeler, R. H.
  - Extension Teaching, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Extension Teaching, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Extension Teaching, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Extension Teaching, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Faculty (Agriculture), 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    Schurman, J. G.
  - Faculty (University), 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    Hammond, William A.
  - Farm Bureau, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    Babcock, H. E.
  - Farm Crops, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    Montgomery, F. G.
  - Farm Crops, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Farm Crops, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Farm Crops, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Farm Management, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Warren, G. F.
  - Farm Management, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Farm Practice, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Stone, John L.
    King, Asa C.
  - Farm Practice, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Floriculture, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    White, Edward A.
  - Floriculture, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Forestry, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Hosmer, Ralph S.
    Spring, Samuel N.
  - Forestry, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - General, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - General, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - General, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - General (Buildings and Grounds, Fire Protection), 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Graduate School, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Creighton, J. E.
  - Heads of Departments, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Heads of Departments, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Home Economics, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Information Service, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    Greens, R. W.
    Adams, Bristow
  - Information Service, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Information Service, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Information Service, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Landscape Art, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    Davis, E. G.
    Curtis, R. W.
  - Law College, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Library (College), 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    Ellis, W. W.
  - Library (University), 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Medical College, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Meteorology, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Military Science, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Music Department, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Quarles, James T.
  - Plant Breeding, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    Emerson, R. A.
  - Plant Breeding, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Plant Breeding, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Plant Pathology, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    Whetzel, H. H.
  - Plant Pathology, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Plant Pathology, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Plant Pathology, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Plant Pathology, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Plant Pathology, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Pomology, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    Chandler, W. H.
  - Pomology, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    Rice, James E.
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Publications Committee, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Reading Course for the Farm (Reports), 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Reading Course for the Farm (Reports), 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Reading Course for Farm House (Reports), 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Registrar (University), 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Rural Economy, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    Lauman, G. N.
  - Rural Economy, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Rural Education, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    Works, George A.
    Griffin, Frederick L.
  - Rural Education, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Rural Education, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Rural Education, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Rural Education, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Rural Education, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Rural Education, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Rural Education, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Rural Engineering, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    Riley, Howard W.
    Robb, B. B.
  - Rural Engineering, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Semi-Centennial Executive Committee, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Abstracts, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Adam, B. (Printed Matter), 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Savage, E. S.
  - Arts and Sciences, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Attorney, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Botany, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Burritt, M. C., 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Burritt, M. C., 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Burritt, M. C., 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Burritt, M. C., 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Burritt, M. C., 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Burritt, M. C., 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Burritt, M. C., 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Burritt, M. C., 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Business Office, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Committee on University Policy, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Comptroller (Cornell), 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Cornell Countryman, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Curtis, G. E., 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Dairy Industry, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Drawing, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    Baker, W. C.
  - Entomology, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    Needham, J. G.
  - Extension Teaching, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Faculty (Agriculture), 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Faculty (Agriculture), 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Faculty (University), 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Farm Crops, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Farm Management, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Farm Practice, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Farm Practice, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Floriculture, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    Lumsden, David
  - Forestry, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Forestry, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Forestry, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Graduate School, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    Creighton. J. E.
  - Hall of Zoology and Entomology, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Heads of Departments, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Heads of Departments, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Heads of Departments, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Heads of Departments, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    Rose, Flora
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Home Economics, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Information Service, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Atwood, M. V.
  - Information Service, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Information Service, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Information Service, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Information Service, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Information Service, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Information Service, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Information Service, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Information Service, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Landscape Art, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Davis, E. Gorton
  - Landscape Art, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Law College, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Woodruff, E. H.
  - Library (College), 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Library (College), 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Library (College), 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Library (College), 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Medical College, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Kerr, A. T.
  - Meteorology, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Wilson, Wilfred M.
  - Meteorology, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Music Department, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    Dann, Hollis
  - Plant Breeding, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Plant Breeding, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Plant Breeding, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Plant Breeding, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Plant Breeding, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Plant Breeding, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Plant Industry Building, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    Galloway, B. T.
    Kidd, Franklyn J.
  - Plant Industry Building, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Plant Pathology, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Whetzel, H. H
  - Plant Pathology, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Plant Pathology, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Plant Pathology, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Plant Pathology, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Plant Pathology, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Plant Pathology, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Plant Pathology, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Pomology, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Pomology, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Pomology, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Pomology, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Publications Committee, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    Reddick, Donald
  - Registrar (University), 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Rural Economy, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Rural Economy, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Rural Education, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    Works, G. A
  - Rural Education, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Rural Education, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Rural Education, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Rural Education, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Rural Education, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Rural Education, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Rural Education, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Rural Education, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Rural Education, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Rural Education, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Rural Education, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Rural Engineering, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Rural Engineering, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Rural Engineering, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Rural Organization, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    Sanderson, Dwight
  - Rural Organization, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Rural Organization, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Rural Organization, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Sage College, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    White, Georgia L.
  - Semi-Centennial Committee, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Semi-Centennial Committee, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Semi-Centennial Committee, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Semi-Centennial Committee, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - J. G. Schurman (President), 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - J. G. Schurman (President), 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - J. G. Schurman (President), 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - J. G. Schurman (President), 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - J. G. Schurman (President), 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - J. G. Schurman (President), 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - J. G. Schurman (President), 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Secretary (College), 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Secretary (College), 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Secretary (College), 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Secretary (College), 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Secretary (College), 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Secretary (College), 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Secretary (College), 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Secretary (University), 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Secretary (University), 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Sibley College, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Soils, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Soils, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Soils, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Soils, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Soils, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Summer School, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - University Christian Association, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    Edwards, Richard H.
    Livermore, Paul S.
  - University Christian Association, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - University Christian Association, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Vegetable Gardening, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Veterinary College, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Abstracts, 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    Hopper, H. A.
  - Animal Husbandry, 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Attorney (University), 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Botany, 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Botany, 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Budget, 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Buildings and Grounds (General), 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    Hiscock, E. T.
    Hurlbutt, A. G.
  - Buildings and Grounds (General), 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Buildings and Grounds (General), 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Buildings and Grounds (General), 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Business Office (1919), 1919 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Business Office (1919), 1919 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Business Office (1920), 1920 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Business Office (1920), 1920 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Business Office (June-July 1919), 1919-06-1919-07 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Business Office (August 1919), 1919-08 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Business Office (August 1919), 1919-08 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Business Office (September 1919), 1919-09 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Business Office (September 1919), 1919-09 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Business Office (September 1919), 1919-09 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Business Office (October 1919), 1919-10 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Business Office (October 1919), 1919-10 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Business Office (October 1919), 1919-10 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Business Office (November 1919), 1919-11 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Business Office (November 1919), 1919-11 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Business Office (December 1919), 1919-12 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Business Office (December 1919), 1919-12 (Box 11, Folder 60)